Young Master.
Get out of the way.
You guys go first.
Chase them!
Oh no!
Shen Tianbai.
Blood.
Getting stronger.
Shen Tianbai.
Wolf.
What's wrong with you?
Shen Tianbai.
[Eclipse in the Lost City]
[Episode 22]
Shen Tianbai.
I found the antidote.
You can't sleep.
Look at me.
I found the antidote.
If...
if
one day,
I
turn...
turn into a monster,
Lu Ye,
you'll have to
kill...
kill me.
Want to die?
It's not that easy.
I haven't settled the score with you
for lying to me.
I won't let you die.
You'll get better soon.
Feeling better?
Shen Tianbai.
What's wrong?
What a wonderful show.
Go.
Shen Tianbai, listen to me.
Shen Tianbai.
Wake up.
Don't worry.
It's not contagious.
Lu Ye.
Do you think he's still the Shen Tianbai
you knew?
He is no longer human.
He is a beast.
This is all thanks to you.
I'll tell you everything.
Fake
antidote.
S04.
Kill.
Old friend.
After all these years,
we still have this tacit understanding.
I know you'd rather die
than give up your scientific ideals.
Rest assured.
I will definitely create a real werewolf.
For you,
for them,
and even more for myself.
So,
this is poison,
and also the antidote.
Of course,
you can also call it S-04.
This experiment is divided into 2 stages.
The first stage, Wolfbane.
According to the lunar cycle,
the body changes,
which can be relieved with
a general maintenance dose.
As for the second stage,
wolf transformation.
As the name suggests,
after the wolf transformation,
the test subject will become
a real werewolf.
Enhanced senses.
Doubled strength.
It's simply the best weapon.
A normal maintenance dose is not enough.
At this time, a special maintenance dose
is needed.
Otherwise,
he is just a beast.
He'll bite others to death
and exhaust himself.
You're digging your own graves
by doing this.
Do you think the foreigners don't know?
With this,
even the fiercest wolf will become a dog.
Now Shen Tianbai is delirious.
Only the one who blows it
will be safe from his attacks.
This experiment actually started
a long time ago.
At first, it was animals,
then it was humans.
The more people die,
the more accurate the data will be.
When the onset occurs,
how long it lasts,
and how they die.
Then came the killers of the Shisha Gang.
They are physically very strong.
Very tough.
No wonder you injected maintenance doses
of different strengths.
From S01 to S03.
If they survived, you increased
the strength.
If they didn't, they died.
Your goal is to find someone
who can perfectly withstand
the wolf transformation.
Dealing with smart people is simple.
I don't even need to explain
for you to understand.
Among so many people,
only Shen Tianbai could survive S-03.
I couldn't wait to let him try S-04.
And he actually did it.
He is the only one in Ningcheng
who successfully tranformed.
Lu Ye,
since you are so smart, take a guess.
What is the most special thing
about the transformation?
It's irreversible.
There is no antidote after wolfification.
He will be a monster
for the rest of his life.
As long as I have
the new maintenance doses,
his life
will be in my hands.
What do you want?
What do I want?
I want to cooperate with a smart person
like you.
Do me a favour.
I know you won't let Shen Tianbai die,
right?
I will give you time to think about it.
Let's go.
Tell the foreigners
the wolf transformation has succeeded,
and we are using his blood
to upgrade the Wolfbane.
Also, tell them not to worry.
The antidote left by the director
is enough.
Yes.
Miss Xu, where are you going?
I need to go out.
Sir ordered
you cannot go out without his permission.
Are you going to follow me
back to my room too?
Thank you, Director, for getting me out.
Xu Qingdao is dead.
Do you know why?
Because of betrayal.
So what to do next,
do you know?
Director.
Please,
spare my life.
I...
I am very useful.
I can help you manage the Shisha Gang.
From now on,
I will do whatever you say.
Give me a chance, Director.
Director.
♪ The lost soul is exiled by the night ♪
♪ It looks up and only sees
the rusted moon ♪
♪ The wind blows across the wilderness,
carrying an echo ♪
♪ Where does the lone wanderer go? ♪
♪ At the edge of the abyss,
through the veil of thick fog ♪
♪ It cries out, refusing to let go ♪
♪ Trying in vain to make me surrender ♪
♪ And the final glimmer of hope ♪
♪ As bells ring out, the old world falls ♪
♪ Tear through the dark
to safeguard the dawn ♪
♪ Chasing the light ♪
♪ And breaking through disorientation ♪
♪ Against the wind, we forge
a brand‑new chapter ♪
♪ Who prays with palms pressed together? ♪
♪ Who grants me
the strength of redemption? ♪
♪ Faith ♪
♪ Bursting forth in blazing dawn light ♪
You're here.
Have you thought it over?
What do you want me to do?
I made a new Wolfbane reagent
with Tianbai's blood.
It used to take a long time,
but now it only takes one injection.
In half a month, we can screen accurately.
This efficiency is simply perfect.
With such a good thing,
shouldn't we expand the scale?
I chose a place as a test area.
What do you think?
I want you to lock down that place.
No mistakes are allowed.
What's next?
What?
After Tianjiu Alley,
where is next?
You will know when the time comes.
Like I said,
I can give you more than you imagine.
As long as you agree,
I will not only give Shen Tianbai
the maintenance dose,
but also let him run the Shisha Gang.
Compared to Lu Wenbiao and Xu Qingdao,
you two young men are more outstanding.
And your friendship is deeper.
This is what I appreciate most.
I sincerely want to cooperate with you.
The foreigners protect me,
I protect you,
and the whole Ningcheng will be ours.
Life will get better and better.
You can revive the Qingtian Gang
and also save Shen Tianbai.
Why not?
Lu Ye,
you are a smart man.
Are the lives of strangers more important,
or is Shen Tianbai's life more important?
I need to see Shen Tianbai
before I give you an answer.
Okay.
No problem.